module.exports = [
    {
        question: `In which country would you find the Palace of Peace and Reconciliation?`,
        answer: `Kazakhstan`,
        wrongAnswers: [`Egypt`, `France`, `Japan`],
    }, {
        question: `Lead Singer Tom Delonge left the band Blink 182 and started a new band called....`,
        answer: `Angels & Airwaves`,
        wrongAnswers: [`Airstreams & Angels`, `Angels & Airstreams`, `Airwaves & Airstreams`],
    }, {
        question: `In season 2 of Stranger Things, what did Dustin name the pollywog?`,
        answer: `D’Artangan`,
        wrongAnswers: [`Porthos`, `Orthos`, `Aramis`],
    }, {
        question: `George Hood set the Guiness Book of World Records for what exercise?`,
        answer: `Planks`,
        wrongAnswers: [`Push-ups`, `Pull-ups`, `Sit-ups`],
    }, {
        question: `Joseph Pullitzer awarded the the first ‘Pullitzer Prize’ to French Ambassador Jean Jules Jusserand for a book on what?`,
        answer: `American History`,
        wrongAnswers: [`Politcal Theory`, `Natural Science`, `Religion`],
    }, {
        question: `What species of marsupial is known to sleep 18-22 hours per day?`,
        answer: `Koala Bear`,
        wrongAnswers: [`Kangaroo`, `Wallaby`, `Wombat`],
    }, {
        question: `What NBA player has scored the most points in their career?`,
        answer: `Kobe Bryant`,
        wrongAnswers: [`Michael Jordan`, `Kareem Abdul-Jabbar`, `Lebron James`],
    }, {
        question: `Which planet in our solar system has the shortest day?`,
        answer: `Jupiter`,
        wrongAnswers: [`Venus`, `Mars`, `Saturn`],
    }, {
        question: `Who was ruling England during the American Revolution?`,
        answer: `King George III`,
        wrongAnswers: [`Queen Victoria`, `King George II`, `King Henry V`],
    }, {
        question: `What alcoholic beverage is typically distilled from sugarcane or molasses?`,
        answer: `Rum`,
        wrongAnswers: [`Vodka`, `Gin`, `Beer`]
    },

];
